https://knittingtraditions.com/about-knitting-traditions/privacy-policy/

Workshops
Workshop ListWorkshop CalendarBeth's Vermont RetreatsSchool of Knitting TraditionsTeaching Trips Abroad & on CruisesKnit-Along Classes for
Local Yarn Shops!Host A Workshop With Beth
Knitting Resources
Knitting Resources IntroSchool of Knitting TraditionsIrish AranDanish KnittingScottishBritish GanseySwedish KnittingNorwegian KnittingSocksMittensOtherYarn SourcesKnitting GlossaryGarment CareVideo Tutorials
My Favorite LinksAbout Knitting Traditions
About UsAbout Beth
Beth’s BackgroundBeth’s Knitting PhilosophyPattern DesignerAuthor and Teacher
Beth's BlogNewsletterEventsBecome A Patron on Patreon.comBeth’s 2013 Kickstarter CampaignTestimonialsPresentations, Interviews, Articles, and PodcastsPrivacy PolicyContact Us
Who we are
Our website address is: https://knittingtraditions.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Ordering Products
If you purchase a product from this site, we will collect information from you to complete your order including payment, shipping, and contact information.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Who we share your data with
If you’ve opted in to our newsletter, your email address, first and last name, and address (if you’ve given it) are saved on iContact.com, the newsletter publishing site used by Knitting Traditions.
Your info given to process an order is retained on our web site so we can process and follow up on your order. It is not shared with any third parties.
How long we retain your data
For users that register on our website as part of the ordering process, we store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (although they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.  Our policy is to retain customer data no longer than 16 months.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have placed an order, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
How we protect your data
This site uses security software and SSL (https) to insure the security of data stored on our web site.
My CartSearch Products
Search for:
Search
Search the whole site
Search for:
Product categoriesBooks & DVDs (4)
Kits (20)
Glove Kits (5)
Hat Kits (1)
Mitten Kits (8)
Other Kits (1)
Sock Kits (6)
Miscellaneous (7)
The Christmas Shop (3)
Vermont Products (2)
Patterns (58)
Garment Patterns (14)
Glove Patterns (5)
Hat Patterns (4)
Mitten Patterns (19)
Scarf Patterns (4)
Sock Patterns (11)
Tools (63)
Garment Care (6)
Needles (37)
Notions (18)
Yarn Management (4)
Traditional Knitting (69)
British Gansey (13)
Cowichan (4)
Danish (1)
Estonian (2)
Irish Aran (5)
Latvian (8)
Norwegian (8)
Other Traditions (8)
Scottish (9)
Swedish (13)
Yarn (0)
Get the newsletter Subscribe to Beth’s monthly newsletter for workshops, videos, tips and tricks, and more.
Subscribe Now
Contact Beth Knitting Traditions
PO Box 124
Putney, VT  05346
Email Beth
©2020 Knitting Traditions / Site by MuseArts
Free Pattern Download
Free Pattern
Gansey Fingerless Mitts
Subscribe to our newsletter and we’ll give you a free pattern download for our Gansey Fingerless Mitts. The Knitting Traditions newsletter is published once (and occasionally two times) per month and is chock full of tips, ideas, and gorgeous knitting projects from Beth. As our way of saying thanks, we’ll give you the Gansey Fingerless Mitts pattern to try right away. (Please note the pattern link will expire in 48 hours, so please download it immediately.) We think you’re going to love traditional knitting!
Click here to sign up and get your free pattern.
Thanks for visiting Knitting Traditions!
CLOSE
